

ALDO ALGHIFARI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- 085717912710
- aldoalghifari24@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/aldoalghifari
- Karawang, West Java, Indonesia



A software developer experience in building websites, UI/UX Designer Undergraduate at HORIZON University majoring in Informatics.

Can work in a team as well as individually, interested to learn new things related to technology, honest, and hard working.



EDUCATION

(2022-Now)
Horizon university Indonesia
Informatics

(2013-2016)
Vocational High School 1 Karawang
Automobile Technology



EXPERIENCES

Production, PT. TOYOTA MOTOR MANUFACTURING INDONESIA (2021 - 2023)

- Diagnosed and resolved machine malfunctions, minimizing production downtime and maintaining production goals
- Analyzed and optimized production processes to reduce production costs

Production, PT. NT PISTON RING INDONESIA (2019 - 2021)

 Monitored production processes and identified quality issues.

Production, PT. AT INDONESIA (2017 - 2019)

 Set up and operated a variety of CNC machines, including lathes, milling machines.



LICENCES

- Course Software Engineering at RevoU
- Learn Javascript at Dicoding Indonesia
- Learn SQL at Dicoding Indonesia
- Created Back End App at Dicoding Indonesia